

ABDUL EL BALAA

DIGITAL MARKETER



ABOUT ME

I am a skilled digital marketing enthusiast with a passion for driving online success. With hands-on experience in content creation, copywriting, website development, and social media management, I bring a unique blend of creativity and analytical thinking to every project. I am dedicated to delivering measurable results and boosting online presence.



CONTACT

abduljunior1948@gmail.com 083 306 0770

Pringle Road, Milnerton, Tygerhof www.linkedin.com/in/abdul-el-balaa-513620186



EDUCATION

Vega School, Cape Town **BCom in Digital Marketing** 2019- 2022

Milnerton High School



WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship | Head of Marketing The Affiliate Monkey - 2023- Present

Content creation for social media | Copywriting |
Analytics Dashboard | Website creation |
Partner Outreach and onboarding | Competitor
analysis and key metrics | Social media
management | Dashboard reporting | Reporting
Marketing meeting | SEO & Email Marketing

Sales & Business Development Representative

CostCertified - 2022 - 2023

Understanding and promoting company programs | Preparing and submitting sales contracts for orders | Generating leads I Meeting or exceeding sales goals | Qualifying potential new clients I Research & Development | Interact with other sales, marketing, and project delivery staff to collaboratively determine customer needs



SKILLS | EXTRAS

- Social Media Management
- Intermediate WordPress experience
- · Proficient in copywriting
- Partner Outreach and onboarding
- SE0 & Email Marketing
- Website Traffic: Increase of 1200-1900 VPM (3 Months)
- Software experience: SEMRush, Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Google Trends, Google LookerStudio, Canva, Later.com, Keyword Planner